So I am imploring folks to keep their aperture wide
as they are taking in that which the mainstream media
is telling them about the Epstein file.
So one, I hope that folks are not turning this
into a Donald Trump, Jeffrey Epstein situation.
They are two people who are representative
of bigger factions that are representative
of control and domination.
Donald Trump is the white nationalist MAGA corporate movement
of the United States, Jeffrey Epstein, Zionism, and Israel.
So when we are seeing them interacting,
we have to remember that they're interacting on behalf of.
Dropside News, which is an actual reputable journalism source,
has already revealed that this man, Jeffrey Epstein,
was getting all sorts of surveillance deals and whatnot
and was absolutely a representative of Mossad,
which is Israel's CIA.
Please do not let the low-hanging fruit salaciousness
of Donald Trump and Bill Clinton and Jeffrey Epstein distract you
when what you're seeing is a revelation
of the even deeper control that the Israeli government has
over United States legislators and legislation.
Two, I see a lot of y'all regurgitating information
that has been given to you by mainstream media
regarding the Democrats leaking these emails
and doing so with the best intentions,
but lacking a very viable and valuable level of skepticism
about what you're being told.
If someone lies to me,
I'm not going to continue to trust them in the same way
because they have already shown me a propensity to lie.
The Democrats have shown you over and over and over and over again
not only that they have a propensity to lie,
but that they do not care about the welfare of the people.
I'm confused at how just last week,
the Democrats had people saying,
we hate y'all, you didn't stand up for us, etc.
Now this week, they put out these files
and folks are like, oh my God, the Democrats,
and you're not realizing that they're playing with you.
Anything a political party does is for political reasons.
A political party that did not start as a party for the people
does not make decisions for the people.
So I just want to remind you of those two things
as you are taking in information,
as you are forming ideas around these Epstein files,
and of course, as you are deciding
what your action steps are going to be.
Ba-dum-bam!
We're going to fight this out there.
Listen to your people!
Because I hit hard!
Billionaires are the only ones!